Liviu Schera



liviu.schera@gmail.com



0772 131 188



linkedin.com/in/liviu-schera-521b10289



https://liviuschera.github.io

Summary

As a dedicated web developer with six months of experience in digital agencies, I specialize in creating innovative and efficient web solutions. My professional and personal projects reflect a strong commitment to continuous learning and technical excellence.

Key Projects:

- Mundus: A ReactJS app that pulls data from three APIs to provide detailed information about all countries, featuring maps and images.
- Image Recognition App: Full-stack app using a Machine Learning API, React, Express, SQL, and PostgreSQL.
- Gym Outlet: Built with React, Firebase, and Stripe for seamless payment integration.
- Client Website and CMS: Designed a responsive site and CMS with SASS, HTML5, MySQL, and PHP.
- Yoga Studio Website: Developed a site that boosted membership by 15%.
- Custom CMS: Created a CMS as part of my Cert IV assessment.
- Noctis Theme for VS Code: Developed a theme with 1million+ installs on VS Code Marketplace and 500+ stars on GitHub.

I am passionate about leveraging my skills to contribute to impactful projects and dynamic teams.

Check out my full portfolio and my resume here: https://liviuschera.github.io

Experience



IT Technician

System Services

Aug 2022 - Apr 2023 (9 months)

- Providing break/fix services such as:
- Installing and configuring software and computer systems.
- Troubleshoot and resolve issues with software or hardware.
- Perform repairs on various hardware and equipment on various sites across the state
- installation of servers, switches and routers and standard office equipment
- Computer repair and upgrades for PCs, laptops, printers
- Responsible for keeping tickets updated with accurate time and notes to ensure that both the team and the clients are updated on the progress of their installations/repairs



Web Developer

MFDCompany

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020 (3 months)

- Worked on a couple of big entrenched projects using a custom build framework based on Vue.JS
- Responsible for keeping work orders updated with notes to ensure that both the team and the clients are updated on the progress of logged tickets



Dirty Chook

May 2020 - Jul 2020 (3 months)

- Contributed to redesigning itpqld.com built in NuxtJS and Cockpit CMS
- Contributed to building bookkeeping solutions website using VueJS/Nuxt
- Coverted Figma designs to responsive emails with MJML and tested them with Litmus
- Converted Figma UX/UI designs into code

Education



Charles Darwin University

Certifiacate IV, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

Licenses & Certifications

- Foundational C# Microsoft
- (A) Front End Development freeCodeCamp
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery Zero To Mastery Academy

Skills

Reactjs • Analytical Skills • Reliability • Python (Programming Language) • Web Application Development • Databases • Communication • Programming • Front-End Development • PostgreSQL